Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Individuals PE.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- D, 1880-2014; 3.75 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Duncan, James S. (James Stuart), b. 1893, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Duncan, Lewis, 1857-1936, 1904 (Box 6)
  - Dunn, Robert W. (Robert Williams), 1895-, 1927 (Box 6)
  - Dunne, William F., circa 1947 (Box 6)
  - Durant, Will, 1885-1981, 1914 (Box 6)
  - Durr, Clifford J. (Clifford Judkins), 1899-1975, undated (Box 6)
  - Durr, Virginia Foster, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Durrin, Ginny, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Dutt, R. Palme (Rajani Palme), 1896-1974, 1946 (Box 7)
- E, 1922-2003; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Easley, Ralph M., 1922 (Box 7)
  - Eastman, Max, 1883-1969, 1950-1955 (Box 7)
  - Easton, Loyd David, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Ebert, Friedrich, 1929 (Box 7)
  - Edelman, Jacob, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Edelstadt, David, 1866-1892, circa 1954 (Box 7)
  - Edwards, Frank, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Eichenberg, Fritz, 1901-1990, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1879-1955, 1943 (Box 7)
  - Eisler, Gerhart, undated (Box 7)
  - Eisler, Hanns, 1898-1962, undated (Box 7)
  - Eisner, Jack, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Ellis, Fred, 1885-1965, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Elser, Johann Georg, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Emspak, Julius, 1904-1962, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Engels, Friedrich, 1820-1895, 1895, undated (Box 7, Box 34, Folder 16)
  - English, Joseph B., circa 1938 (Box 7)
  - Engstrand, Stuart David, 1905-1955, 1936 (Box 7)
  - Epstein, Edwin M., 1980 (Box 7)
  - Epton, Bill, circa 1976 (Box 7)
  - Erenburg, Ilia, 1891-1967, 1949 (Box 7)
  - Erlich, Henryk, 1882-1941, 1934-1943 (Box 7)
  - Ernst, Morris Leopold, 1888-1976, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Erskine, Lillian, undated (Box 7)
  - Ervin, Lorenzo Kom'boa, undated (Box 7)
  - Estelle, Helen G. H., 1974 (Box 7)
  - Evans, Ahmed, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Evers, Medgar Wiley, 1925-1963, 1963-1970 (Box 7, Box 34, Folder 17)
- F, 1909-2017; 2.75 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Faber, Gustav, undated (Box 7)
  - Fábáin, Béla, 1889-1967, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Fagan, Myron C. (Myron Coureval), b. 1887, 1949 (Box 7)
  - Fanelli, Giuseppe, 1909-, undated (Box 7)
  - Farberstein, Leonard, 1964 (Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 27)
  - Farmer, Fyke, undated (Box 7)
  - Farmer, James, 1920-, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Farrell, James T. (James Thomas), 1904-1979, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Fasanella, Ralph, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Fast, Howard, 1914-2003, 1941 (Box 7)
  - Faubus, Orval Eugene, 1910-1994, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Faulk, John Henry, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Faure, Sébastien, 1858-1942, undated (Box 7)
  - Fedotoff, Theodore, circa 1918 (Box 7)
  - Feigenbaum, Benjamin, 1860-1932, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Feiler, Arthur, 1938 (Box 7)
  - Feinberg, Israel, 1937 (Box 7)
  - Feinglass, Abe, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Feinstein, Henry, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Feinstone, Morris C., 1935 (Box 7)
  - Feinstone, Sol, 1888-1980, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Feiss, Richard A., 1916 (Box 7)
  - Felberbaum, Arthur, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Feldman, Herman, 1894-1947 (Box 7)
  - Felicani, Aldino, 1891-1967 (Box 7)
  - Feliciano, Carlos (Committee to Defend), 1972 (Box 7, Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Fels, Joseph, 1854-1914 (Box 7)
  - Ferguson, Duncan, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Ferrat, Andre, 1936 (Box 7)
  - Ferrer y Guardia, Francisco, 1909 (Box 7)
  - Ferrero, Vincent, undated (Box 7)
  - Ferry, Elinor, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Ferry, W.H., 1965 (Box 7)
  - Feuer, Lewis (Box 7)
  - Fey, Harold Edward, 1898-, 1963 (Box 7)
  - Fiedler, Leslie A., 1959 (Box 7)
  - Fielding, Wiliam J. (William John) 1886- (list of pamphlets), 1972 (Box 7)
  - Fieldman, Solomon, undated (Box 7)
  - Fierro, Anthony, circa 1933 (Box 7)
  - Filene, Edward A., undated (Box 7)
  - Fine, Benjamin, 1905-, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Fine, David, circa 1977 (Box 7)
  - Fine, Fred M., undated (Box 7)
  - Fine, Nathan S., 1930 (Box 7)
  - Finkelstein, Norman G., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Finley, Ira Monroe, 1886-1981, undated (Box 7)
  - Finley, William, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Firestone, Shulamith, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Fischer, Louis, 1896-1970, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Fischer, Ruth, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1879-1958, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1867-1947, 1911 (Box 7)
  - Fishman, Sam, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Fitch, John A. (John Andrews), 1881-1959, 1909 (Box 8)
  - Fitzgerald, M. Eleanor (Mary Eleanor), 1877-1955, 1919 (Box 8)
  - Fitzpatrick, John, 1870-1946, undated (Box 8)
  - Flanagan, Hallie, 1890-1969 (Box 8)
  - Flanders, Allan, undated (Box 8)
  - Flanders, Ralph E. (Ralph Edward), 1880-1970, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Fleischman, Harry, 1959 (Box 8)
  - Flores Magón, Ricardo, 1873-1922, 1913 (Box 8)
  - Flory, Ishmael, 2004 (Box 8)
  - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, 1938, undated (Box 8)
  - Foner, Diane, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Foner, Henry, 1988-2017 (Box 8, Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Foner, Jack D., 2000 (Box 8)
  - Foner, Moe, 1915-, 1993, undated (Box 8)
  - Foner, Philip Sheldon, 1910-1994, 1963, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Ford, Henry, 1863-1947, 1921 (Box 8)
  - Forer, Joe, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Forman, James, undated (Box 8)
  - Foster, William Z., 1881-1861, 1910-1955 (Box 8, Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Fox, Irving David, 1950 (Box 8)
  - Frank, Miriam, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Frank, Richard, 1937 (Box 8)
  - Frank, Waldo David, 1889-1967, undated (Box 8)
  - Fraser, Clara, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Freeman, Everette J., 1984 (Box 8)
  - Freeman, Joseph, 1897-1965 (Box 8)
  - French, Burton L., 1920 (Box 8)
  - French, Eleanor Clark, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Fried, Emanuel, 1913- I, 1954, undated (Box 8, Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Fried, Emanuel, 1913- II, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Friedman, Esther Grosshandler, 1962 (Box 8)
  - Friedman, Samuel H., 1897-1990 (Box 8)
  - Frome, Michael, 1946 (Box 8)
  - Frost, Robert, 1874-1963 (Box 8)
  - Frow, Edmund and Ruth, 1997 (Box 8)
- G, 1877-2007; 4 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes
  - Gaitskell, Hugh, 1906-1963 (Box 8)
  - Galbraith, John Kenneth, 1908-2006, circa 1960 (Box 8)
  - Gale, Lynn A.E. (Defense Committee), undated (Box 8)
  - Galenson, Walter, 1914-1999, 1961 (Box 8)
  - Galíndez, Jesús de, 1915-1956 (Box 8)
  - Gallacher, William, 1881-1965 (Box 8)
  - Galleani, Luigi, 1861-1931, undated (Box 8)
  - Galvin, Miles E. (Miles Eugene), 1926-, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Gandi, Indira, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Gandhi, Mahatma, 1869-1948, 1944 (Box 8)
  - Garbarino, Joseph William, 1919-, 1950 (Box 8)
  - Gardner, John W., 1965 (Box 9)
  - Garibaldi, Giuseppe, 1807-1882, 1906 (Box 9)
  - Garland, Charles, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Garrison, Ben, undated (Box 9)
  - Garry, Charles R., 1991 (Box 9)
  - Garson, Barbara, circa 1970 (Box 9)
  - Garvey, Marcus, 1932- (Box 9)
  - Gary, Elbert H., undated (Box 9)
  - Gary, Romain, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Garza, Hedda, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Gates, John, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Gaulle, Charles de, 1890-1970, 1937 (Box 9)
  - Gebert, Boleslaw, 1895-, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Geldman, Max, undated (Box 9)
  - Gelderloos, Peter, undated (Box 9)
  - Gellers, Don C., 1938 (Box 9)
  - Gellert, Hugo, 1892-1985, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Gellhorn, Walter, 1939 (Box 9)
  - Genovese, Eugene D., 1930-, 1965 (Box 9)
  - George, Harrison, 1948 (Box 9)
  - George, Henry, 1839-1897, 1877 (Box 9)
  - Gerber, G. August, undated (Box 9)
  - Gerber, Julius, 1940 (Box 9)
  - Germer, Adolph, 1917 (Box 9)
  - Gerson, Simon W., 1994 (Box 9)
  - Gettleman, Marvin E. I, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Gettleman, Marvin E. II, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Ghent, William J. (William James), 1866-1942, 1908 (Box 9)
  - Giambalvo, Alberto, 2007 (Box 9)
  - Gil, David G., 1976 (Box 9)
  - Gilbert, Leon, undated (Box 9)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Giovannitti, Arturo M., 1884-1959 and Ettor, B.F., 1913- (Box 9)
  - Giovannitti, Len, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Gitlow, Benjamin, 1891-1965, 1939 (Box 9)
  - Glaberman, Martin, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Glass, Dan, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Glazer, Joe, undated (Box 9)
  - Gleason, Thomas W., 1968 (Box 9)
  - Glotzer, Albert, 1908-1999 (Box 9)
  - Glueck, Bernard, b. 1883, 1923 (Box 9)
  - Glueck, Sheldon, 1896-, 1927 (Box 9)
  - Godwin, William, 1906 (Box 9)
  - Goebel, George H., 1924 (Box 9)
  - Gold, Ben, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Gold, Michael, 1894-1967 (Box 9)
  - Goldberg, Chaim, 1971 (Box 9)
  - Goldberg, Dennis, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Goldberg, Louis P. (Louis Palatnik), b. 1888, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Goldbloom, Maurice J., circa 1957 (Box 9)
  - Golden, Clinton S. (Clinton Strong), 1888-1961, 1946 (Box 9)
  - Golden, Harry, 1902-, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Goldman, Emma, 1869-1940 I, 1908 (Box 9)
  - Goldman, Emma, 1869-1940 II, 1990- (Box 9)
  - Goldmark, Pauline Dorothea, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Goldstein, Bernard, undated (Box 9)
  - Goldstein, David, 1913 (Box 9)
  - Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris), 1909-1998, 1962 (Box 9)
  - Goldwater, Walter, 1964 (Box 9)
  - Goldway, David, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Gollancz, Victor, 1893-1967 (Box 9)
  - Gomberg, William, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Gompers, Samuel, 1850-1924, 1908 (Box 9)
  - Goodman, Paul, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Goodwin, William and Mary Wollenstonecraft, 1906 (Box 9)
  - Gordon, Max, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Gorky, Maksim, 1868-1936, 1932, undated (Box 10, Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Gottlieb, Harry, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Gourevitch, Boris, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Grafton, Samuel, 1907-, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Gramsci, Antonio, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Grayson, Victor, undated (Box 10)
  - Greeley, Horace, 1811-1872, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Green, Archie, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Green, Gil, 1906-, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Green, John C., 1951 (Box 10)
  - Green, William, 1872-1952, 1925 (Box 10)
  - Greenberg, Noah, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Greene, Felix, undated (Box 10)
  - Grimes, Nikki, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Grinko, G. F. (Grigory Fedorovich), 1890-1938, 1933 (Box 10)
  - Grogan, William, undated (Box 10)
  - Gronlund, Laurence, 1846-1899, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Gropper, William, 1897-, 1940 (Box 10)
  - Gross, Feliks, 1944 (Box 10)
  - Grossman, Jonathan, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Gruenberg, Benjamin C. (Benjamin Charles), 1875-1965 (Box 10)
  - Gruening, Ernest, 1887-1974, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Guerrero, Antonio 1958-, circa 2001 (Box 10)
  - Guevara, Ernesto, "Che" 1928-1967, 1962 (Box 10)
  - Guillaume, James, undated (Box 10)
  - Guinan, Matthew, circa 1952 (Box 10)
  - Guthrie, Woody, 2004 (Box 10)
  - Gutman, Herbert George, 1928-, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Guttoso, Renato, undated (Box 10)
- H, 1883-2006; 3.5 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Hackett, Frances, 1936 (Box 10)
  - Hager, Don J., 1956 (Box 10)
  - Hagerty, Thomas J. (Thomas Joseph), circa 1904 (Box 10)
  - Hague, Frank, 1876-1956, 1938 (Box 10)
  - Hahn, Herman J., 1888-1948, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Haig, Robert Murray, 1887-1953, 1926 (Box 10)
  - Haire, Robert W., undated (Box 10)
  - Haldane, J. B. S. (John Burdon Sanderson), 1892-1964, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Haldeman-Julius, E. (Emanuel), 1888-1951, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Hall, Bolton, 1854-1938, 1923 (Box 10)
  - Hall, Burton, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Hall, Gus, 1949-2000 (Box 10)
  - Hall, Paul, undated (Box 10)
  - Hamer, Fannie Lou, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Hammarskjold, Dag, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Hampton, Fred, 1948-1969 (Box 10)
  - Hand, Learned, 1872-1961 (Box 10)
  - Hanford, Ben, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Hanna, M. A., undated (Box 10)
  - Hard, William, circa 1913 (Box 10)
  - Hardie, J. Keir, undated (Box 10)
  - Harding, Warren G. (Warren Gamaliel), 1865-1923, 1964 (Box 10)
  - Hardman, J. B. S. (Jacob Benjamin Salutsky), 1882-1968, 1931 (Box 10)
  - Hardy, George, 1911-, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Harman, Moses, undated (Box 10)
  - Harney, G. Julian (George Julian), 1817-1897, undated (Box 10)
  - Harriman, Averill, 1958 (Box 10)
  - Harrington, Michael, 1928-1989, 1958 (Box 10)
  - Harrison, Austin, undated (Box 10)
  - Harrison, Hubert H., 2000 (Box 10)
  - Harrison, J. Max, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Hart, Philip A. (Philip Aloysius), 1912-1976, 1961 (Box 10)
  - Hartmann, George W. (George Wilfried), 1904-1955, 1940 (Box 10)
  - Hass, Eric, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Hathaway, C. A. (Clarence Albert), b. 1892, 1941 (Box 10)
  - Havarius, Stratus, 1981 (Box 10)
  - Hawkins, Howie, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Hawkins, Yusuf, undated (Box 10)
  - Hayden, Tom, 1961-1975 (Box 10)
  - Hayes, Max S., 1866-1945, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1881-1954, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Haywood, Big Bill, 1869-1928, undated (Box 10)
  - Haywood, Harry, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Hazard, John N. (John Newbold), 1909-, 1938 (Box 10)
  - Healey, Dorothy, 1914-2006, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, 1863-1951, 1919 (Box 11)
  - Hedges, M. H. (Marion Hawthorne), b. 1888, 1940 (Box 11)
  - Hegedüs, András, 1922-, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Heighton, William, b. 1800, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Heikkinen, Knut, undated (Box 11)
  - Heimann, Eduard, 1889-1967, 1939 (Box 11)
  - Heine, Heinrich, 1797-1856, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Held, Adolph, 1948 (Box 11)
  - Helfgott, Roy B., 1961 (Box 11)
  - Heller, Philip Alter, 1911-1976, undated (Box 11)
  - Hemingway, Ernest, 1899-1961, 1937 (Box 11)
  - Henderson, Donald, undated (Box 11)
  - Hendrickson, Kenneth E., 1970 (Box 11)
  - Hepner, Adolf, undated (Box 11)
  - Herberg, Will, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Herbers, John, 1964 (Box 11)
  - Herling, John, 1939 (Box 11)
  - Herndon, Angelo, 1935, undated (Box 11)
  - Herron, George Davis, 1862-1925, undated (Box 11)
  - Hersey, John, 1914-1993, 1946 (Box 11)
  - Hervé, Gustave, 1871-1944, 1911 (Box 11)
  - Hess, Karl, 1923-, undated (Box 11)
  - Hester, Hugh B. (Hugh Bryan), 1895-1983, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Hewes, Amy, 1877-1970, 1923 (Box 11)
  - Heywood, Ezra H. (Ezra Hervey), 1829-1893, 1883 (Box 11)
  - Hicks, Granville, 1901-1982, 1939 (Box 11)
  - High, Stanley, 1938 (Box 11)
  - Hill, Charles A. Jr., 1951 (Box 11)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1924- I, 1951- (Box 11)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1924- II, 1951- (Box 11)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1924- III, 1951- (Box 11)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1924- IV, 1951- (Box 11)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1924- V, 1951- (Box 11)
  - Hill, James C., undated (Box 11)
  - Hill, Joe, 1879-1915 (Box 11)
  - Hill, Norman, 1933-, 1993 (Box 11)
  - Hill, Stanley, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Hillman, Bessie, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Hillman, Sidney, 1887-1946, 1929-1987 (Box 11, Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Hillquit, Morris, 1869-1933, 1917 (Box 11)
  - Hillquit, Nina, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Himes, Chester, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Hindus, Maurice Gerschon, 1891-1969, 1945 (Box 11)
  - Hirsch, Mark D., 1958 (Box 11)
  - Hiss, Alger, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Hồ, Chí Minh, 1890-1969 I, 1947-1972 (Box 12, Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Hồ, Chí Minh, 1890-1969 II, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Hoan, Daniel W. (Daniel Webster), 1881-1961 (Box 12)
  - Hobby, Wilbur, undated (Box 12)
  - Hobsbawm, E. J. (Eric J.), 1917-, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Hobson, J. A. (John Atkinson), 1858-1940, 1918 (Box 12)
  - Hochman, Julius, 1892-1970, 1943 (Box 12)
  - Hodge, Everette, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Hodson, William, 1891-1943 (Box 12)
  - Hoffa, James R. (James Riddle), 1913-, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Hoffman, Abbie, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Hoffman, S. L., 1960 (Box 12)
  - Hogan, Austin P., 1941 (Box 12)
  - Hogan, J. C., undated (Box 12)
  - Holcombe, A. N., 1910 (Box 12)
  - Holdridge, Herbert, undated (Box 12)
  - Holmes, Lola Belle, undated (Box 12)
  - Holmes, John Haynes, 1879-1964, 1934 (Box 12)
  - Holodnak, Mike F., 1974 (Box 12)
  - Hood, Thomas, 1799-1845, 1904 (Box 12)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1902-1989 I, 1932 (Box 12)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1902-1989 II, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Hoopes, Darlington, 1896-, 1962 (Box 12)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964, 1945 (Box 12)
  - Hope, John II, 1957 (Box 12)
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1955 (Box 12)
  - Horne, Lena, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Horowitz, David, 1939-, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Horowitz, Irving Louis, undated (Box 12)
  - Hosmer, Harriet Goodhue, 1830-1908, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Hourwich, Isaac Aaronovich, 1860-1924, 1911 (Box 12)
  - Houston, Charles Hamilton, 1895-1950 (Box 12)
  - Howard, Harry Paxton, 1942 (Box 12)
  - Howard, Sidney Coe, 1891-1939, 1921 (Box 12)
  - Howe, Bertha W., 1906 (Box 12)
  - Howe, Frederick C., 1916 (Box 12)
  - Howe, Irving, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Howells, William, undated (Box 12)
  - Hoxha, Enver, 1908-1985 (Box 12)
  - Huberman, Gertrude Heller, 1965 (Box 12)
  - Huberman, Leo, 1903-1968, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Hudson, Roy, 1941 (Box 12)
  - Hughan, Jessie Wallace, 1875-1955, 1916 (Box 12)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948, 1937 (Box 12)
  - Hughes, Emmet John, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Hughes, Langston, 1902-1967, 1938 (Box 12)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978, 1948 (Box 12)
  - Hunt, H.L., 1964 (Box 12)
  - Hunter, Robert, 1874-1942, 1910 (Box 12)
  - Hurst, Fred, undated (Box 12)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1965 (Box 12)
  - Huxley, Aldous, 1894-1963, 1958 (Box 12)
  - Hyde, Douglas, circa 1958 (Box 12)
  - Hyde, Henry M., 1912 (Box 12)
  - Hyman, Sidney, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Hyndman, Henry Mayers, 1910 (Box 12)
  - Hyun, David, circa 1955 (Box 12)
- I, 1877-2002; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Ibsen, Henrik 1828-1906, [1928] (Box 13)
  - Ilchuk, Frank H., 1991 (Box 13)
  - Imani (Johnny Harris), 1977 (Box 13)
  - Ingerman, Sergius M., 1943 (Box 13)
  - Ingersoll, Robert G., 1877 (Box 13)
  - Inglis, Agnes, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Innis, Roy, 1934-, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Irish, Jane, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Isacson, Leo, 1946 (Box 13)
  - Isca, Ida Pilat, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Isca, Valerio, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Ishill, Joseph, 1962 (Box 13)
  - Isserman, A. J. (Abraham J.), 1934 (Box 13)
  - Iushewitz, Morris, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Ives, Burl, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Ives, Irving McNeil, 1896-1962, 1957 (Box 13)
- J, 1904-2005; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Jackson, George (Soledad Brothers), 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Jackson, James E., 1914-2007, 1940 (Box 13)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1941-, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Jacobs, Aletta H. (Aletta Henriette), 1854-1929, undated (Box 13)
  - Jacobs, Paul, 1959 (Box 13)
  - Jacobson, Julius, undated (Box 13)
  - Jacoby, Johann, undated (Box 13)
  - Jaffe, Naomi, 1968 (Box 13)
  - Jaffe, Philip J. (Philip Jacob), 1895-1980, undated (Box 13)
  - Jagan, Cheddi, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Jaksch, Wenzel, 1896-1966, undated (Box 13)
  - James, C. L. R. (Cyril Lionel Robert), 1901-1989 I, 1946 (Box 13)
  - James, C. L. R. (Cyril Lionel Robert), 1901-1989 II, 1981 (Box 13)
  - James, Ralph C., 1929-, and James, Estelle, 1964 (Box 13)
  - Jara, Victor, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Jasny, Naum, 1883-1967, 1942 (Box 13)
  - Jászi, Oszkár, 1875-1957, undated (Box 13)
  - Jaurès, Jean, 1859-1914, 1924 (Box 13)
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1909 (Box 13)
  - Jerome, V.J., 1946 (Box 13)
  - Jezer, Marty, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Jiang, Kanghu, 1883-1954, undated (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Alvin Saunders, 1874-1971, 1959 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Arnold, 1989 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Hewlett, 1874-1966, 1949 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Howard "Stretch", 2000 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, J. B., circa 1975 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Lewis Jerome, 1915 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973, 1964 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Malcolm, 1948 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Oakley C., b. 1890, 1962 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Olive M. (Olive Malmberg), 1872-1954, 1919 (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Ralph, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Johnston, Eric A. (Eric Allen), 1895-1963 (Box 13)
  - Joliot-Curie, Frederic, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Jonas, Alexander, 1904 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Claudia, 1949 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Ellis O., 1967 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Glenda, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Joe, 1937 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Mary Hoxie, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Mother, 1837-1930, 1925 (Box 13)
  - Jones, Valerie, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Joseph, Joe, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Josephson, Ben, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Josephson, Leon, 1898-, 1957 (Box 13)
  - Jubran, Amer, circa 2002 (Box 13)
- K, 1889-2008; 3.25 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Kabakchiev, Khristo, 1878-1940, 1921 (Box 13)
  - Kagan, Samuel, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Kahn, Alexander, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Kahn, Sara Rosenbaum, 1962 (Box 13)
  - Kahn, Tom I, 1960 (Box 13)
  - Kahn, Tom II, 1967 (Box 13)
  - Kahn, Tom III, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Kaiser, Ernest, 1956 (Box 14)
  - Kaler, Emil, undated (Box 14)
  - Kallen, Horace Meyer, 1882-1974, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Kampelman, Max M., 1920-, 1946 (Box 14)
  - Kantorovits, Hayim, 1933 (Box 14)
  - Kaplan, Irving, 1900-1988 (Box 14)
  - Karenga, Maulana Ron, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Karlin, William, 1818 (Box 14)
  - Kartsen, Diana, 1948-2007 (Box 14)
  - Katayama, Sen, 1975 (Box 14, Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Katsh, Abraham Isaac, 1908-, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Kautsky, Karl, 1854-1938 I, 1899 (Box 14)
  - Kautsky, Karl, 1854-1938 II, 1899 (Box 14)
  - Kautsky, Karl, 1854-1938 III, 1899 (Box 14)
  - Kawakami, Jōtarō, 1889-1965, undated (Box 14)
  - Keating, Kenneth B. (Kenneth Barnard), 1900-1975, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Keell, Thomas H., 1919 (Box 14)
  - Kelber, Harry, 2006 (Box 14)
  - Keller, Helen, 1880-1968, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Kelley, Augustus M., 1959 (Box 14)
  - Kelley, Florence (Chief Justice of the Court of Domestic Relations), 1903 (Box 14)
  - Kellor, Frances A., 1911 (Box 14)
  - Kelly, Harry, undated (Box 14)
  - Kempton, Murray, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Kennan, George F. (George Frost), 1904-2005, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Kennard, Clyde, circa 1961 (Box 14)
  - Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963, 1956 (Box 14)
  - Kennedy, Joseph S., undated (Box 14)
  - Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Kerensky, Aleksandr Fyodorovich, 1881-1970, 1920 (Box 14)
  - Kerr, Clark, 1911-2003, 1958 (Box 14)
  - Kessler-Harris, Alice, 1991 (Box 14)
  - Keynes, John Maynard, 1946 (Box 14)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita Sergeevich, 1894-1971 I, 1957 (Box 14)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita Sergeevich, 1894-1971 II, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita Sergeevich, 1894-1971 III, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Khrushchev, Nikita Sergeevich, 1894-1971 IV, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Kien, Nguyen, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Kilpatrick, William Heard, 1871-1965, 1961 (Box 14)
  - King, Carol Weiss, 1993 (Box 14)
  - King, Dennis, 1979 (Box 14)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., Rev. 1929-1968, 1962-1968 (Box 14, Box 35, Folder 4)
  - King, Mel, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Kingston, Steve, undated (Box 14)
  - Kinoy, Arthur, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Kinshasa, W. E., undated (Box 14)
  - Kirchwey, Freda, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Kirkendoll, Robert L., 1950 (Box 15)
  - Kirkland, Lane, 1954 (Box 15)
  - Kirkpatrick, George R. (George Ross), 1867-1937, undated (Box 15)
  - Kirkpatrick, T. C., 1948 (Box 15)
  - Kirkpatrick, William H., 1941 (Box 15)
  - Kirrane, William, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Kirshbaum, Louis, undated (Box 15)
  - Kitz, Frank, undated (Box 15)
  - Klare, Michael T., 1942-, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Klein, Henry L., undated (Box 15)
  - Kliche, Josef, 1919 (Box 15)
  - Knoles, George Harmon, 1941 (Box 15)
  - Knopf, Blanche W., 1894-1966 (Box 15)
  - Knorr, Klaus, 1911-1990, 1957 (Box 15)
  - Kobbe, Herman, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Kochubiyevsky, Boris, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Kocmata, Karl F, 1920 (Box 15)
  - Kohler, Herbert V., 1961 (Box 15)
  - Kokkalis, Alexander, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Kolarov, Vasil Petrov, 1877-1950, 1948 (Box 15)
  - Kolatch, Myron, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Kolko, Gabriel, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Kollontai, A. (Aleksandra), 1872-1952, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Kollwitz, Käthe, 1867-1945, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Konvitz, Milton Ridvas, 1908-, undated (Box 15)
  - Kopkind, Andrew D., 1994 (Box 15)
  - Koppersmith, [Hal?], 1980 (Box 15)
  - Korolkoff, Sergei, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Kossuth, Lajos, 1802-1894, circa 1952 (Box 15)
  - Kovnator, Ray, 1944 (Box 15)
  - Kozak, Jan, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Krafft, Frederick, circa 1918 (Box 15)
  - Kramer, Dale, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Kramer, Leon, 1889-1962, undated (Box 15)
  - Kramer, Louise, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Kramer, Sam, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Kramer, Samuel P., undated (Box 15)
  - Kraus, Arthur James, b. 1896, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Kris, Ernst, 1900-1957, 1941 (Box 15)
  - Kristol, Irving, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Krofta, Kamil, 1937 (Box 15)
  - Kropotkin, Petr Alekseevich, 1842-1921 I (Box 15)
  - Kropotkin, Petr Alekseevich, 1842-1921 II, 1962 (Box 15)
  - Krumbein, Charles, undated (Box 15)
  - Kucinich, Dennis J., 1946-, 2008 (Box 15)